Ann Satterthwaite Papers PBY037 PBY037
Stage
Ann Satterthwaite Papers
1968-1986
Stage
PBY037
5 Linear feet
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Materials donated by Anne Satterthwaite in November 1999.
Scope and Contents
Collection of files assembled by donor in the course of volunteer work on the Georgetown Waterfront Commission, 1968-1986.
- Series 1
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Background, 1979-1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Waterfront Park, 1978-1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Miscellaneous, 1980-1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Rosewood Hotel I - legal briefs., 1985 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Rosewood Hotel II - correspondence and other documents., 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - National Park Service - park plans and hearings., 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - National Park Service - Park Environment Assessment., 1984 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - National Park Service and Washington Harbor Associates I - Exchange of interest in land between., 1984 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - National Park Service and Washington Harbor Associates II - Exchange of interest in land between., 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - National Park Service and Washington Harbor Associates III - correspondence., 1980-1984 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - National Park Service and Washington Harbor Associates IV - appraisals., 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Park land transfer, 1985-1987 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Parking plan, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Delegate Walter Fauntroy, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - U.S. Army, 1978-1984 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Sen. Mark Hatfield's bill - Sheffect vs. County of Los Angeles (photocopy), 1980 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Sen. Mark Hatfield's bill - Sheffect vs. County of Los Angeles (photocopy), 1970 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Floodplain, 1976-1984 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Floodplain - - pamphlets and booklets. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Floodplain - memos and correspondence. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Environmental Assessment, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Environmental Assessment - public hearing. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Environmental Assessment - Report on Georgetown Studies., 1933 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Environmental Assessment - correspondence. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Historic Preservation, 1977-1981 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Historic Preservation - notes. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Historic Preservation - Report on Georgetown Studies., 1933 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Historic Preservation - correspondence. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Historic Preservation Review Board, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Council of Fine Arts, 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Council of Fine Arts - correspondence. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Council of Fine Arts - H.R. 4947. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Council of Fine Arts - Brief History of the Georgetown Waterfront Development Proposal. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Miscellaneous, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Miscellaneous - newspaper clips. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Miscellaneous - correspondence. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Miscellaneous - Pisataway Park, MD, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Miscellaneous - "Capital Comments" newsletter, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Miscellaneous - list of Georgetown Waterfront development commitments. (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Miscellaneous - reply brief for federal appellants in Committee of 100 on the Federal City, et al. v. the Secretary of the Interior, et al. (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Interior Department documents, 1983-1985 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Interior Department documents - Environmental Assessment. Exchange of Easements in Land between the National Park Service and Washington Harbour Associates. (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Interior Department documents - Appraisal Review, Proposed Exchange of Interests with the Washington Harbor Associates, Georgetown Waterfront. (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Georgetown Waterfront - Interior Department documents - Proposed Exchange of Land Interests between National Park Service and Washington Harbor Associates with the Georgetown Waterfront Park. (Box 4, Folder 20)